

Rafael A. Dimatz

Computer System Engineer

Mobile Phone: (0291) – 155267939 E-mail: rafael.dimatz@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 23/01/1979

Address: Ramirez Urtasun 1865

City: Bahia Blanca **Nationality:** Argentina

Objective

My goal is to continue developing and acquiring knowledge that allows me to achieve both personal and professional growth facing new challenges and work experiences.

Dedicated, proactive, passionate and skilled at working with distributed teams using Agile methodologies.

Education

COMPUTER SYSTEM ENGINEER

2008

Universidad Nacional del Sur – Bahía Blanca, Bs As

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN SPECIALIZED ON ACCOUNTING

1997

Escuela Técnica N 2 – Bahía Blanca, Bs As

LANGUAGUE SKILLS - Intermediate B1

Work History

COMVIVA (Bahía Blanca)

2017- Actual

Role

Developer Front End (React)

Technologies

REACT (Hooks, Custom Hooks, Fetch, Axios, Redux, Sagas, use Effect, use Context, Form, Local Storage, Props, State, Template String, Destructuring, Spread, React Router Formik, Yup, Redux Toolkit, Autho)

Material UI/Boostrap 4/Materialize/Styled Components/Ajax

Framework ExtJS/MVVM/CSS/HTML/ JavaScript/JSON/

Scrum Master/GIT/JIRA

REST API/NodeJS express (Mongoose, MySQL, cors, router)

REST API/Java/Spring Boot /Apache Tomcat/SoapUi/

Linux/SQL SERVER/MongoDB

Methodologies

Agile (Scrum)

Responsibilities

Build consoles based on provided specifications.

Rafael A. Dimatz / RESUME Page | 2

Description

Console Telecomunication

RHPro (RAET) - Bahia Blanca, Bs As

2010 - 2017

Role

Web Ssr Developer (Scrum Master).

Technologies

ASP / VB 6.0 / Crystal Reports / SQL SERVER / JavaScript / JQuery / HTML / HTML5 / CSS / CRM / ISO / VSTS / POO / WCF / C#.

Methodologies

Agile (Scrum).

Responsibilities

Build applications based on provided specifications. Document the construction of software components. Build your own test cases. Run unit testing. In charge of the system configuration. Specify customization needs. RH Pro Migrator Product Specific Functionality. Analysis and resolution of incidents using SQL and reading of ASP codes, to update the Database of Clients. Analyze customer needs, technical, font and database troubleshooting, font integration and testing, version migrations.

Description

Human resources web application.

FREELANCE - Bahia Blanca, Bs As

2009 - 2014

Role

Developer.

Technologies

VB 6.0 / SQL SERVER.

Methodologies

Agile (Scrum).

Responsibilities

Development of Trade Management Systems.

Description

TMS that includes Tax Billing, Customers /Suppliers, Bank accounts, Products/Stock and Reports modules.

CONTROL SERVICE – Bahia Blanca, Bs As

2008 - 2009

Role

Developer.

Technologies

Rafael A. Dimatz / RESUME Page | 3

VB 6.0 / SQL SERVER.

Methodologies

Agile (Scrum).

Responsibilities

Team Leader.

Description

Human resources and access control systems.

OLEAGINOSA MORENO S.A-Bahía Blanca, Bs As

2007 - 2008

Role

Technical Consultant.

Responsibilities

Help Desk.

Description

LAN and Control Workstation Management.

Windows XP, Windows 2000/2003 Server installation and configuration, TCP / IP configuration.

Microsoft Office installation.

PC Hardware Troubleshooting

Additional Tools: Lotus Notes, Active Directory.

Education Teacher

Institute Juan 23

2015 - Continue

Role Teacher Description

Subject: Data Base

UTN (Universidad Tecnológica Nacional)

2022 - Continue

Role Teacher Description

Subject: Programming 3 (POO – Java)

Course Creando 4 proyectos con React JS

2021

Courses

Course Aprender React JS desde cero con ejemplos practicos

2021

Course React JS de cero a experto creando aplicaciones reales	2021
Course Aprender MongoDB – Udemy	2020
Course Aprender React JS – Udemy	2020
Course Git y la Terminal de comandos - Udemy	2019
Course Aprender Bootstrap 4 de Cero a Experto – Udemy	2020
Course SQL Basico – Intermedio - Udemy	2019
Certified Scrum Master (CSM) - Scrum Alliance	2019
Course Java - Udemy	2018
English Course Intermediate Level - Bahia Idiomas	2018
English Course Intermediate Level - Tudor House Institute	2015 – 2016
Agile Scrum Methodology Course.	2016
Web Design WordPress Content Management System.	2016
Course .NET Introduction to MVC 5 (Company Globant)NET Junior Control Course F Cessi	2015 2010
Intermediate Java Course Sun Proydesa - UTN	2009
Microsoft Technological Seminary in .Net Architecture - UNS	2003